

YASH SAROHA

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

CONTACT

7988008862

yashsaroha966@gmail.com

Linkedin: yash-saroha

GitHub: YashSaroha

SKILLS

C / C++ / JavaScript Data Structures & Algo **OOPS** Concept Front-end Development **Back-End Development** Git and GitHub WordPress

PROJECTS

Team Engineers

team-engineers.cleverapps.io Created a website to provide study material for college students

Internship Projects

- · Commerce Insights
- Sarvhitt India
- Police Mitra Trust
- EyeTurners
- Asma Energy
- Dhajcraft
- TaxArena
- Cognosmed
- ARvillage
- AngelOne Patna
- Sunday Rest
- · Eateria Cafe
- Sobhraj Construction and many more...

PROFILE

Currently serving as a WordPress Developer Intern with more than 1 year of experience having keen interest in Full Stack Web Development. Design and develop awesome looking & completely responsive websites having intermediate knowledge of Data Structures and Algorithms.

EDUCATION

B.E in Electronics & Communication 2020 - Ongoing Current CGPA - 8.44 **UIET**, Panjab University Senior Secondary - Class 12 2019 - 2020 95.8 % Bright Scholar Sr. Sec. School

Bright Scholar Sr. Sec. School

WORK EXPERIENCE

WordPress Developer

Secondary - Class 10

Techax Labs

- · Design and develop beautiful looking websites using WordPress
- · Integrating plugins and functionalities alongwith managing database and server integration of the website
- Designed over 30+ completely responsive & active websites used by the clients and consumers in today's date

Startup Head

2021 - 2022

Feb 2022 - present

2017 - 2018

96.2 %

E-Cell, UIET, Panjab University

- Collaborating with 20+ startups in near-Chandigarh region and helping them out by providing team support
- · Successfully organised InternFair, an event to actively hire college students for internships and part-time or full-time jobs

Member of Technical Team

2020 - 2021

E-Cell, UIET, Panjab University

- Designed and developed frontend part of E-Cell club website
- Managing and pushing changes to GitHub profile of the club